technogerms.com 2015-12-04

# Privacy Policy | TechnoGerms

The privacy of our visitors to  **TechnoGerms.com**  is important to us.

At   **TechnoGerms** , we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit  **TechnoGerms** , and how we safeguard your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.

## Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

## Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [Network Advertising](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

  *   *   *   *   *   *
